Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ypsilanti
  - Manchester Hardware store, Y 152 --; Copy neg. (Box 5)
C 24.1, C 24.2, C 24.3, C 25.11, CM, 10.1, CM 33
St. Patrick's Catholic Church
B 120, B 121
St. Paul Street
B 93
St. Paul's Church
CM 4, CM 58, S 548
St. Thomas Catholic Church
AA 237, AA 369, AA 480, AA, 711
St. Thomas School
AA 221.29, AA 369
Stadium
AA 196.2, AA 700
Staebler
AA 88, AA 254.7, AA 254.8, AA 254.9, AA, 273.35, AA 683, AA 689, CM 28, DI 36
Staebler Oil Company
AA 254.7, AA 254.8, AA 254.9, AA, 689, CM 28, DI 36
Staebler and Sons
AA 88, AA 683
Stage Coach
Y 88
Stand Tower
Y 15
Standard Oil
CM 22
Starkweather Hall
Y 7
State Savings Bank
AA 118, AA 160
State Street
AA 2.29, AA 13, AA 16, AA 32A, AA 32C, AA 32D, AA 32E, AA 34C, AA 42, AA 47, AA 63, AA 70, AA 75
AA 117, AA 121, AA 142, AA 147, AA 148, AA 153, AA 154, AA 156, AA 158, AA 170, AA 174, AA 175, AA 177, AA 181, AA 187, AA 191, AA 192
AA 200, AA 202, AA 203, AA 204, AA 205, AA 221.1, AA 221.6, AA 221.12, AA 221.14, AA 221.18, AA 221.19, AA 221.32, AA 226.1, AA
230.2, AA 230.3, AA 230.5, AA 230.6, AA 230.7, AA 230.8, AA 230.10, AA 231.1, AA 231.2, AA 231.3, AA 231.4, AA 234, AA 243, AA 244.1
AA 251.3, AA 251.5, AA 251.8, AA 251.12, AA 251.13, AA 251.17, AA 251.20, AA 251.21, AA 251.25, AA 251.28, AA 251.29
AA 252.3, AA 254.4, AA 254.7, AA 254.8, AA 254.9, AA 273.35, AA 279, AA 289
AA 317, AA 366, AA 371, AA 372, AA 390
AA 410, AA 435, AA 456, AA 457, AA 484, AA 503.1, AA 599
AA 627, AA 630, AA 663, AA 676, AA 679, AA 680, AA 699, AA 711, AA 718
Stattan
CM 2.4
Statue
AA 406, AA 406
Stauch
AA 264D
Steam Engine
AA 168, CM 86, M 104, Y 35
Stebbins House
DE 51, DE 76
Steel
AA 441
Steinbach
DE 71
Stewart
B 140
Streetcars, see also Interurbans
AA 160, AA 162, AA 1, AA 165, AA 172, AA232.10A,232.10B, AA 232.10C, AA 232.10D, AA 371,377, AA 378, AA 379, AA 446, AA 523
Student Life
AA 2.30, AA 2.31, AA 2.32, AA 2.43, 2.43, AA 2.44, AA 2.44, AA 2.45, AA 2.45,2.46, AA 2.46, AA 45, AA 207, AA 254.5,255.7, AA 412, AA 412, AA 670, AA 672, AA680, AA 702, AA 703, AA 704
Stuhrberg
B 46, B 53, B 54, B93
Stuhrberg and Balore Meat Market
B 53, B 54
Sturm
S 45
Sturm's Harness Shop
S 45
Sugar Bowl Restaurant
AA 232.9, AA 326, AA327
Summer
AA 14, DI 30, M 52, S 55, Y 93
Summit Street
AA 508, C 1.13
Sunset Avenue
AA 230.11
Sunset Boulevard
AA 593
Sunset Road
AA 3
Superior Dairy
AA 325
Sutton
M 116
Swaine
Y 125
Sweet
Y 54
Sweet's Dry Goods Store
Y 54
Swift Street
AA 242
Swimming
B 74, B 142, B 143
Sylvan Township
C 27
Taft
AA 2.36, AA 2.36, AA 2.37, AA 2.37, AA 255.9, 255.9
Tailor
C 3.14
Tappan Hall
AA 2.2
Tappan School
AA 706
Tappan Street
AA 712
Taxicab
AA 26E, AA 26E, AA 450
Taylor
S 29
Teachers
B 57, B 91, B 100, B 103, B 111, B 117, B, 119, C 2.9, DI 24, DI 26, M 54, M 61, M 91, M 117, S 25
Telephone Company
M 65
Telephone Operator
AA 198
Tennis
AA 273.12
Tepper
Y 82
Territorial Road
DE 28, DE 45
Texaco
CM 74
Thayer Street
AA 221.30, AA 273.56, AA 273.59
Theater and Theaters
AA 64, AA 81, AA 82, AA 241.7, 291, AA 322, AA 323, AA 452, AA 499, AA 500, AA 643, AA 644, AA 645, AA 646, AA 647, AA, 648, AA 649, AA 651, AA 652, AA 653, AA 654, AA 655, AA 656, AA 657, AA 719
CM 43, CM 7, DE 54, Y 85, Y 140, Y 141, Y 143, Y 149
Third Ward
AA 28A, AA 28C
Third Ward School
AA 27B
Thirty-First Infantry
Y 109, Y 113
Thompson
B 113
Thompson Dodge
Y 79
Thompson Farm Machinery
Y 97
Thompson and Thompson Gristmill
B 113
Thornton
Y 24
Threshing Machines
DE 38, DE 43
Tintypes
AA 478, C 2.12, C 15.6, S 17, S 45
Toledo Railroad
AA 119, AA 221.26
Tompkins
C 2.13
Torch Papers
AA 530, AA 530, AA 531, AA 531, AA 532, AA 532, AA 533, AA 533, AA 534, AA 534, AA, 535, AA 535, AA 536, AA 536, AA 537, AA 537, AA 538, AA 538, AA 539, AA 539, AA 540, AA, 540
Tornadoes
AA 300.1, AA 300.2, AA 300.3, C 3.21, C, 3.22, C 16.1, CM 89, CM 90, DI 44, DI 45, 141, Y 142, Y 143, Y 145, Y 146, Y 147, Y, 148, Y 149
Town Hall
B 32, C 13.8, M 21
Towne's Apple Drying House
M 101
Towner
Y 57
Townline School
DI 17
Township Clerk
M 81
Township Library
M 112
Track
AA 2.27
Track Race
AA 2.27
Training School
Y 15
Transforming Station
S 12
Traub
M 17
Traver
AA 27D
Traver Road
AA 482, AA 487
Trinity Lutheran Church
AA 709, S 1
Trucks
AA 5, AA 130, AA 137, AA 162, AA 232.3. AA, 232.5, AA 232.6, AA 258.6, AA 270.2, AA 325, AA 504.1, AA 504.2
B 134, CM 2.1, CM 2.2, 9, CM 24, CM 35, CM 54, S 42, Y 59
Tunnels
B 31, B 106
Twentieth-Century Club
M 108
Subject Index: U-Z
UM Alumnus
AA 2.38
UM Campus
AA 185D, AA 185F, AA 200, AA 211, AA 212, AA 213, AA 221.32, AA 228.15, AA 228.16, AA, 234
AA 251.18, AA 251.19, AA 251.20, AA, 251.21, AA 251.22, AA 251.23, AA 251.24, AA, 251.26, AA 251.27, AA 251.28, AA 251.29
AA252.1, AA 254.5, AA 255.1, AA 255.2, AA 255., AA 255.6, AA 255.8, AA 273.5, AA 273.8, AA, 273.32, AA 273.45
AA 366, AA 372, AA 456, 503.1, AA 506.1, AA 506.2, AA 506.3, AA 670, AA 699
UM Diagonal
AA 142, AA 228.3, AA 251.11, AA 251.19, 251.23, AA 255.2, AA 255.5, AA 503.1
Ulrich
AA 245
Union Bank
M 22
Union Depot
M 74
Union High School
AA 251.5f
Union Railroad
M 74
Union School
B 2, B 89, C 3.18, DE 4, DE 5, DE 25, DE 80, S 23
Unitarian Church
AA 273.26
University Hall
252.3, AA 2.29, AA 61, AA 212, AA, 221.12, AA 251.13, AA 251.22, AA 251.29, AA, 273.4, AA 273.17, AA 273.22, AA 273.41, AA, 406, AA 467, AA 503.4
University Hall
AA 667
University High School
AA 273.49, AA 273.49
University Hospital
AA 29J, AA 244.23, AA 273.7, AA, 273.20, AA 273.46, AA 273.48, AA 273.62, AA, 273.63, AA 273.64, AA 338, AA 339, AA 368, 427
University Libraries, see also Libraries
AA 2.19, AA, 2.21, AA 273.11C, AA 273.11C, AA 391, AA 43, AA 463
University Museum
AA 273.53, AA 409
University Switch Engine
AA 511
University Towers
AA 196.2, AA 196.4, AA 196.5, AA, 247.1, AA 247.2, AA 247.3, AA 247.4, AA 247, AA 247.6
University of Michigan
AA 2.1, AA 2.2, AA 2.3, AA 2.4, AA 2.5, AA 2.6, AA 2.7, AA 2.8, AA 2.9, AA 2.10
AA 2.11, AA 2.12, AA 2.13, AA 2.14, AA 2.15, AA 2.16, AA 2.17, AA 2.18, AA 2.19
AA 2.20, AA 2.21, AA 2.21, AA 2.22, AA 2.22, AA 2.24, AA 2.24, AA 2.25, AA 2.26, AA 2.27, AA 2.29
AA 2.30, AA 2.31, AA 2.32, AA 2.34, AA 2.35, AA 2.36, AA 2.37, AA 2.38, AA 2.40
AA 2.40, AA 2.42, AA 2.43, AA 2.44, AA 2.45, AA 2.46, AA 29J, AA 45
AA 58, AA 61, AA 72, AA 73, PAA 117, AA 121, AA 142, AA 161, AA 175, AA 183, AA 185, AA 185C, AA 185D, AA 185F, AA 188, AA 196.2, AA 196.3
AA 205, AA 207, AA 211, AA 212, AA 213, AA 221.12, AA 221.27, AA 221.28, AA 221.31, AA 221.32, AA 226.2, AA 227, AA 228.3, AA 228.5, AA 228.6, AA 228.15, AA 228.16, AA 232.3, AA 232.5, AA 232.6, AA 234, AA 243, AA 246
AA 251.11, AA 251.13, AA 251.18, AA 251.19, AA 251.20, AA 251.21, AA 251.22, AA 251.23, AA 251.24, AA 251.26, AA 251.27, AA 251.28, AA 251.29, AA 252.1, AA 254.5
AA 255.1, AA 255.2, AA 255.3, AA 255.5, AA 255.6, AA 255.7, AA 255.8, AA 255.9, AA 255.10, AA 255.11, AA 265
AA 273.1, AA 273.2, AA 273.3, AA 273.4, AA 273.5, AA 273.6, AA 273.7, AA 273.8, AA 273.9, AA 273.10, AA 273.11A, AA 273.11B, AA 273.11C, AA 273.11D, AA 273.12, AA 273.13, AA 273.14, AA 273.15, AA 273.17, AA 273.18, AA 273.19, AA 273.20
AA 273.21, AA 273.22, AA 273.28, AA 273.29, AA 273.32, AA 273.34, AA 273.37, AA 273.39
AA 273.41, AA 273.42, AA 273.43, AA 273.44, AA 273.45, AA 273.46, AA 273.47, AA 273.48, AA 273.50
AA 273.53, AA 273.55, AA 273.62, AA 273.63, AA 273.64, AA 273.65A, AA 273.65B, AA 273.66, AA 273.67
AA 296, AA 330, AA 338, AA 339, AA 363, AA 365, AA 366, AA 368, AA 372, AA 373, AA 374, AA 375, AA 390, AA 392, AA 391
AA 404, AA 405, AA 406, AA 407, AA 408, AA 409, AA 412, AA 427, AA 431, AA 431, AA 455, AA 455, AA 456, AA 462, AA 463, AA 466, AA 467, AA
503.1, AA 503.4, AA 506.1, AA 506.2, AA 506.3, AA 511, AA 551, AA 552, AA 553B
AA 650, AA 650, AA 658, AA 667, AA 670, AA 672, AA 675, AA 677, AA 678, AA 679, AA 699
AA 700, AA 701, AA 701, AA 702, AA 703, AA 704, AA 705
University of Minnesota
AA 462
University of Pennsylvania
AA 392, AA 700
Unter Kircher Block
M 102
Van Boven
AA 688
Van Netter
DE 112
Van's Marine Band
AA 26A
Van's Restaurant
AA 26A
Vanderlip
B 144
Varsity Laundry
AA 23, AA 504.1, AA 504.1, AA 504.2, AA 504.2
Varsity Restaurant
AA 241.4
Vermont
CM 69
Veterans
C 2.5, C 23, DE 65, M 122
Village Orchestra
CM 10.3
Vinkle
DE 56, DE 71
Vinkle House
DE 56
Vinkle-Steinbach Home
DE 71
Vivienne Farms
AA 715
Vogel
422, AA 424, AA 425, AA 426, C1.22
Vogel Meat Market
AA 424, AA 425, AA 426
W.H. McDermott Carriage Works
Y 49
W.H. McDermott Horse Shoeing
Y 49
WHL Roberts Tavern
Y 91
WL McCullough Company
AA 290
WP Schenk Company
C 15.4, C 22.4
WP Schenk and Company
C 1.17
Wackenhut
C 2.11
Wadham
AA 266.1
Wadhams, Ryan & Reule Menswear
AA 266.1
Wagner
AA 2.41, AA 31A, AA 302, AA 468, AA 519.1, 38, DE 39, DE 79, DE 112
Wagner Cider Mill
DE 112
Wagner and Biermann Machine Shop
AA 468
Wagner and Brothers Blacksmith
AA 519.1
Wagons
AA 221.11, AA 245, DI 5, DI 41, Y 96
Wahoo Baseball Club
DE 110, DE 111
Wahr
AA 117, AA 552, AA 553A
Wahr and Miller Footwear
AA 553A
Wahr's Books
AA 117
Walker
AA 26B, AA 26D, AA 125, S 48
Walker Building
AA 125
Walker Carriage Factory
AA 19, AA 20
Walker Furniture
C 1.21, C 1.28, C 8.2, C 8.3
Walker's Livery
AA 26C, AA 26D
Wall Street
AA 29M, AA 29T, AA 41, AA 221.5, AA, 231.11, AA 244.3, AA 483, AA 505.1, AA 505.2, AA 538
Wall Street Bridge
AA 244.3, AA 505.1, AA 505.2
Walsh Street
AA 557
Walton Home
M 35
War-Related Photos
AA 227, DE 94, M 71, M 122, Y 81, Y 90, Y 97, Y 103, Y 109, Y 113, Y 137
Ward School
M 57, M 96
Warner
CM 69, Y 88
Washington Block
AA 244.2
Washington Street
AA 27, AA 34E, AA 55, AA 56, AA 57, AA 91, AA 89, AA 103, AA 103A, AA 103B, AA, 103C, AA 118, AA 123, AA 131, AA 160, AA 161, AA 177, AA 192
AA 218, AA 220, AA 221.19, 221.30, AA 241.1, AA 241.3, AA 244.2, AA, 244.2, AA 251.51 AA 288, AA 302, AA 305, AA
468, AA 496, AA 558, AA 559, AA 567, AA 638, AA 639, AA 717
M 60
Y 17, Y 18, Y 44, Y, 74, Y 86, Y 93, Y 129
Washtenaw Art Works
AA 291
Washtenaw Avenue
AA 49, AA 185, AA 196.3, AA 273.24, AA 273.26, AA 273.54, AA 273.66, AA 510, AA 517, AA 518, 571, AA 573, AA 575, AA 576, AA 577, AA 578, DI 36
Washtenaw County
AA 127, AA 238, AA 241.2, AA 244.29, AA 251.14, AA 418, AA 430
Washtenaw County Atlas
AA 28A, AA 28B, AA 28C, AA 28D
Washtenaw County Board of Supervisors
AA 418
Washtenaw County Courthouse
AA 238
Washtenaw Gas Company
AA 239A, AA 239B
Washtenaw Hotel
AA 29T, AA 221.34, AA 244.16, AA 581
Washtenaw Mill
M 8
Water Towers
AA 168, M 50, M 101, Y 10, Y 150
Water and Electric Company
C 1.28, C 8.2
Waterman Gymnasium
AA 2.3, AA 2.4, AA 185C
Waters
M 54, M 61
Watling
AA 2.30, AA 2.30, AA 255.7
Watson
C 3.14, S 22
Webster
C 3.14
Webster Church
DE 93, DE 100
Webster Tailor
C 3.14
Webster Township
DE 28, DE 45, DE 95, DE 96, DE 97, DE 98
Wedding
AA 597
Weichers General Store
B 76, B 87
Weinlander
M 119
Weinman
AA 529
Weinman and Hoelzle
AA 529
Weinmann Block
AA 126, AA 241.3
Weir
M 91
Weiss
CM 36
Weiss Drugstore
B 99
Weiss Shoe Shop
M 123
Wesleyan Methodist Church
B 68
West Elementary School
B 23
West End Rifle Team
AA 59
West Park
AA 27B, AA 29P, AA 622, AA 623
West Physics Building
AA 2.1, AA 678
West Street
B 30, B 113
Western House
B 19, B 79, B 82
Westfall
Y 117
Wheeler
C 2.9, DE 28, DE 45
Wheeler House
AA 530, AA 532
Whitmore Lake
AA 232.7, AA 272.6, B 45, W 549, W 551, Y 102
Whitmore Lake Bridge
AA 232.7
Whitmore Lake Road
AA 29C
Whitney Theater
AA 64, AA 81, AA 82, AA 452, AA 719
Wild Street
AA 508
Wilgus
AA 2.40, AA 2.42
William Street
AA 29H, AA 32B, AA 173, AA 208, AA 20, AA 210, AA 221.6, AA 222, AA 223, AA 226.1, AA 230.1, AA 230.6, AA 299
AA 433, AA 434, AA 477, AA 609, AA 611, AA 686, AA 687, AA, 709
Willis
W 550
Willits-Zeeb
DI 29
Willitt
DI 39
Winchell
AA 265, AA 273.8
Windmill, see also Mills
AA 221.25
Wines
CM 69
Wing
DE 36
Winter
AA 142, AA 155, AA 169, AA 187, AA 189, AA, 197, AA 375, AA 378, AA 584, AA 589, AA 590, AA 591, AA 592, AA 598
AA 609, AA 626, AA, 627, AA 628, AA 629, AA 630, AA 631, AA 632, AA 633
B 123, CM 13.1, CM 13.2, M 45, M 51, S 31, Y 42
Wolf
C 16.2
Women
AA 113, AA 240, AA 282.1, AA 478, AA 580
B, B 21, B 25, B 30, B 37, B 43, B 47, B 55, 63, B 73, B 75, B 85, B 91, B 96, B 100, 106, B 107, B 108, B 109, B 122
C 2.11, 3.7, C 3.8, C 8.4, C 15.2, C 25.9
CM 23, 44, CM 44, CM 89, CM 90, CM 10.3
D 440, 99, DE 42
DI 39
M 63, M 65, M 88, M 94, 97, M 108, M 113
S 52
Y 82, Y 102, Y 10, Y 127
Women's Athletic Building
AA 273.2, AA 273.21
Women's City Club
AA 273.66
Women's Fieldhouse
AA 273.2
Wood
C 1.31, C 8.1
Woodruff School
Y 37, Y 94, Y 118
Wool
S 9
Wool Company
C 22.3
Wuerthner Clothing Store
M 106
YMCA
AA 479, AA 503.5, AA 716, AA 720, Y 31, Y 31, 130
Yankee Trader
AA 314
Yost
AA 227, AA 462
Youth for Understanding
AA 273.54
Ypsi-Ann
Y 33, Y 50, Y 66
Ypsilanti
AA 93, AA 276
Ypsilanti Auto Parts
Y 49
Ypsilanti Car House
Y 64
Ypsilanti Centennial
Y 25, Y 88
Ypsilanti Dairy Creamery Company
Y 71
Ypsilanti Fire Department
Y 8, Y 35, Y 72, Y 74
Ypsilanti Gas Works
Y 80
Ypsilanti Grain and Elevator Company
Y 38
Ypsilanti Hay Press Company
Y 132
Ypsilanti High School
Y 119, Y 120, Y 121
Ypsilanti Machine Works
Y 136
Ypsilanti Milling Company
Y 123
Ypsilanti Opera House
Y 140, Y 141, Y 143, Y 149
Ypsilanti Post Office
Y 122
Ypsilanti Power House
Y 62, Y 65
Ypsilanti Railroad
Y 34, Y 39
Ypsilanti Water Works
Y 135
Ypsilanti Whist Club
Y 82
Ypsilanti-Hillsdale Railroad
M 25, M 59
The Ypsilantian
Y 57
Zahn
AA 264C
Zeeb
DI 29
Zion Lutheran Church
AA 481, AA 481
Zweigel
Y 6